# David M. Padilla

# Full Stack Web Developer

Over 5+ years of experience establishing personal relationships through communications as well as strong analytical skills for interpreting documentation and data to resolve conflicts. Successful in working both team and self-directed settings. Up-and-coming Full Stack Web Developer ready to make an impact in designing and simplifying the complexities of your applications.

# **Experience**

### 2017-08 - Financial Associate I - Health & Welfare

2018-09

Fidelity Investments

- Analyzed thousands of IBM employee records to uncover hidden solutions unseen by more experienced associates.
- Downgraded critical setbacks into minor hiccups through positive verbiage, empathy, and ownership.
- Recognized by VP of Participant Services to take on more managerial duties such as peer mentorship and procedural write-ups.

# 2014-01 - Scheduling Agent

2017-07

AIG VALIC

- Reestablished communication between advisors and their clients, which in turn resulted in increases to their monthly contributions as well as greater client retention.
- Helped one advisor significantly add over a quarter million in assets from multiple discovery meetings, which was then managed through the company.
- Created new departmental procedures and statistics through Excel to increase performance from both the scheduling staff and supervisor.

### **Education**

## 2018-10 -2019-04

# **University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill**

Coding Boot Camp - Full Stack Web Development Certification

An intensive 24 week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications.

# **Project Highlights**

**CineGrub** is a front-end application that seamlessly integrates the ability to find movies and restaurants nearby via zip code. Users can also save any movie or restaurant result found and send invitations to friends.

https://cinegrub.com/

**Gamelogger** is a full stack application that allows users keep track of their video games in progress. Users can also mark any video game as completed or remove them entirely to make space for newer games.

https://gamelogger-app.herokuapp.com/

**Schedulr** is a full stack application that any client can use to schedule or manage appointments for customers. In addition, clients may also send friendly text reminders to their customer's mobile number. Registration is required. <a href="https://app-schedulr.herokuapp.com/">https://app-schedulr.herokuapp.com/</a>

### **Personal Info**

### **Address**

Raleigh, NC 27615

#### **Phone**

+1 919 869 9647

#### **Email**

davidpadilla.dev@gmail.com

### Website

davidpadilla.io

### **GitHub**

github.com/dpadillajs

### **Technical Skills**

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap 4

JavaScript

ES6

jQuery

Handlebars

React

Node.js

**Express** 

Firebase

NoSQL

MySQL

Sequelize

MongoDB

Mongoose

**Chrome DevTools** 

**RESTful APIs**